{
    "subject": "resource/Impresa_Pizzarotti",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Construction",
    "human_readable": "Impresa Pizzarotti is a type of Construction.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9198660254478455,
            "question": "What type of company is Impresa Pizzarotti?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.914962649345398,
            "question": "Is Impresa Pizzarotti involved in manufacturing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7742127180099487,
            "question": "What industry does Impresa Pizzarotti operate in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6517954468727112,
            "question": "Give an example of a service that Impresa Pizzarotti might provide."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5612172484397888,
            "question": "Can you think of a large-scale project that might require the services of Impresa Pizzarotti?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48543500900268555,
            "question": "Does the name 'Impresa Pizzarotti' suggest anything about its nature?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4114634096622467,
            "question": "How does Impresa Pizzarotti contribute to society?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3451281785964966,
            "question": "What are some skills and expertise needed to work for a company like Impresa Pizzarotti?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2618825435638428,
            "question": "What are some other types of companies that fall under the category of 'Construction'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22745266556739807,
            "question": "What is another term for 'Construction'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Impresa Pizzarotti is a type of Construction.",
            "html": "dbpedia_884_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some other types of companies that fall under the category of 'Construction'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_884_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some skills and expertise needed to work for a company like Impresa Pizzarotti?",
            "html": "dbpedia_884_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does Impresa Pizzarotti contribute to society?",
            "html": "dbpedia_884_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_884_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_884_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_884_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_884_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_884_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_884_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_884_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_884_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_884_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_884_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided clearly indicates that Impresa Pizzarotti & C is involved in the construction industry, including activities such as building residential and non-residential buildings, railway constructions, and other civil engineering works. Therefore, it can be accurately stated that Impresa Pizzarotti is a type of Construction company."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}